Morrow Family papers, 1839-1966
Sophia Smith Collection
- Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow)
  - Morgan, Elisabeth Reeve (Morrow)
    - Biographical materials
      - Checkbook from trip to France, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Welsh menu notebook, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous: invitations, news clippings, driver's license, 1927-35, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Debutante book, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Log book of gifts given and received, 1915-31 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous collected pamphlets, 1921-34 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Easter sermons, prayer, eulogy of Adelaide Landon Roddy, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Llanover House, Abergavenny estate catalogue, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Engagement and Wedding
        - Announcements and news clippings, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, 1932
          - Engagement (Box 8, Folder 4-7)
          - Wedding (Box 8, Folder 8)
        - Financial and legal arrangements, 1932-33 (Box 8, Folder 9)
        - Notebook of wedding gifts, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence to Family
      - Cutter, Annie S. (1877-1957), 1914-34 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Cutter, Annie S. (1845-1938 and 1877-1957), 1915-34 (Box 8, Folder 12-14)
      - Aunt Maud and Uncle Dutch (Mr. and Mrs. Charles Hulst?), 1928-34 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Morgan, Aubrey, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Morgan, "Father," 1934 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Morgan, Margaret, 1933-34 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Morrow, Dwight (father), 1911-28, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter
        - 1910-32 (Box 9, Folder 1-15)
        - 1933-34, undated (Box 10, Folder 1-7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1914-34 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with friends and associates
      - Connor, Charles, 1924-34 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - d'Harnoncourt, Rene, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Dr. Foster, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Lamont, Corliss, 1923-33, undated (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
      - Outgoing, 1923-34 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Incoming
        - 1925-33 (Box 10, Folder 15-17)
        - 1933-34 (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
      - From pupils at Dwight School, 1928-30, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Christmas and greeting cards, 1925-30, undated (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
      - Mexico, 1928-29 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - To "Connie," written 1925-26, compiled and given to ECM in 1948 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Writings
      - Diaries
        - 1914, 1919-20 (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
        - 1921-25, 28, 31 (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
      - Travel journal - poems, 1922-25 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Travel journal, 1926-31
        - Typescript (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
        - Original (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Excerpts from Mexico diary, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Childhood
        - Homemade books, 1910, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - Record book, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - "Elisabeth's book written for Constance," undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Family crossword puzzle, questionnaire, "Reading," 1926, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Notebook with draft for family history, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Contents of card index box compiled by Elisabeth in Pasadena, circa 1934 (Box 13, Folder 8-10)
      - Short Stories
        - "The Daguerreotype" and "Summer by the Sea," undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
        - "Green Sofa Sunday," "Piazza Theatre," etc., undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
        - "Our Mother's Family" (Box 13, Folder 13)
        - "Mexican Children" (Box 13, Folder 14)
        - "Home Again," Charm, May 1930 (Box 13, Folder 15)
        - "When Mother Was a Little Girl" (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
        - The Six of Us, 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 18)
        - The Six of Us, 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Morgan, Janet: correspondence to ECM, 1940-53 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Morrow, Alice: correspondence to ECM, 1903-29, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Morrow, Clara
    - Diary, 1914-17 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1902-11 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Morrow, Dwight Whitney
    - Biographical material
      - Account book and Princeton degree, 1901-25 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Passports, 1921-31 (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
      - New Jersey Senatorial campaign, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Invitations: Naval Conference, London, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - News clippings: Mexico, 1927-32 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, outgoing
      - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter, 1893-14 Mar 1902 (Box 14, Folder 12-16)
      - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter, 16 Mar 1902-1931 (Box 15, Folder 1-7)
      - Family, regarding engagement, 1901 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Family, 1903-29 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Friends and associates, 1912-30 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, incoming, 1908-29 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Jr.
    - Biographical material
      - School papers, etc.1920, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Passport, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Groton School records, 1922-27 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Amherst College commencement, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Harvard Columbus Expedition, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 16)
        [see also: photographs]
    - Correspondence, outgoing
      - Cutter, Annie Spencer (1845-1938 and 1877-1957), 1914-33 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Morgan, Constance Morrow, 1928-34 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Morgan, Elisabeth Morrow, 1932-34 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Morrow, Dwight (father), 1918-31 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Morrow, Elizabeth Cutter, 1915-54 (Box 16, Folder 1-13)
      - Sisters and miscellaneous, 1920-48 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Children of DWM Jr to ECM, 1950-54 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Writings
      - "The Indian Book" circa 1914-22 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Stories for Grotonian, circa 1922-27 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter)
    - Biographical Material
      - General and miscellaneous, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Passports, 1921-48 (Box 17, Folder 3-6)
      - The Interlude high school alumna update, May 1902 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Who's News and Why, Apr 1943 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Wedding, 16 June 1903 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Death
        - Correspondence to Cutter family, 1954-55 (Box 17, Folder 10)
        - Condolences to family, 1954-55 (Box 17, Folder 11)
        - Condolence cards and flowers, 1954-55 (Box 17, Folder 12)
        - Telegrams, 1954-55 (Box 17, Folder 13)
        - Resolutions and tributes from organizations, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence regarding gifts and bequests, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
        - Obituaries and memorial services, 1954-55 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Presbyterian church bulletins and reports, 1875-1940 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Notebooks and address books, undated (Box 18, Folder 1-6)
      - Account books, 1913-21 (Box 18, Folder 7-9)
      - Notes attached to letters by ECM, slips from journals, undated (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
      - Calendar and reminder pad, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Articles and news clippings
        - Committee for address of Women of Great Britain and Ireland on Slavery in the United States, 1852 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Zur Erinnerung an Gardie von Horn geb. Maynard, 1914 (Box 2)
        - Poetry by others, 1911-42 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Preludes to Poetry, Stevenson Room Poetry Group, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous articles and clippings, 1862-1914 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Education
        - Central High School report and Smith College course list, 1890-96 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Smith College class notes
          - Freshman year winter term, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 7)
          - Sophomore year fall, 1893
            - German (Box 2, Folder 8)
            - English Prose and Poetry (Box 2, Folder 9)
            - Zoology (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
          - Sophomore year winter term, Old English, 1894 (Box 20, Folder 1)
          - Junior year fall, 1894
            - Economics (Box 20, Folder 2)
            - Zoology (Box 20, Folder 3)
              - annotated textbook (Box 20, Folder 4)
            - English literature (Box 20, Folder 5)
            - Rhetoric (Box 20, Folder 6)
          - Senior year fall, 1895
            - 19th century prose (Box 20, Folder 7)
            - Aesthetics (Box 20, Folder 8)
            - 19th century history (Box 20, Folder 9)
            - 19th century history (Box 21, Folder 1)
            - Philosophy (Box 21, Folder 2)
          - Senior year spring, 1896
            - Psychology and ethics (Box 21, Folder 3)
            - 19th century history (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
          - Unidentified class notes, possibly English literature, 1895 (Box 21, Folder 6)
          - Notebook on English literature, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
          - Rhetoric notebook, circa 1892-94 (Box 21, Folder 8)
          - Daily Themes and rhetoric ("Bain"), circa 1895 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
        - Smith College student activities
          - Alpha Society, 1895-96 (Box 22, Folder 3)
          - Ancient Order of Hibernians
            - General, 1894-96 (Box 22, Folder 4)
            - Songbook, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - Postgraduate study notes
          - Ibsen lecture course, Oct-Nov 1896 (Box 22, Folder 6-9)
          - European history: Nation-making in the 19th century, 1898 (Box 22, Folder 10-12)
          - French language, circa 1896-1903 (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
          - Spanish language, undated (Box 23, Folder 6-12)
          - Englewood government, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 13-14)
          - Home nursing, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
          - "Bringing up children," 1904-06 (Box 23, Folder 16)
          - List of children's books, circa 1909-14 (Box 23, Folder 17)
        - Religious studies (Box 24)
          - Bible study notebook, 1903-52 (Box 24, Folder 1)
          - Bible notebook: Mark, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
          - Gospel of Luke extension course, 1951-52 (Box 24, Folder 3)
            [see also: oversize, 1954 seminary summer session]
          - Bible study, 1953-54 (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - French, Italian, and German notebook, circa 1911 (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Greek literature notebook, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Poetry course taught by Elizabeth Drew, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Changing Functions of Education, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Family
        - Genealogy, 1929, 1969, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - Weddings, 1903-37 (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - Play: "Mook," performed by children, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 11)
        - Cutter, Annie Spencer (1845-1938): death
          - Condolences to her daughters, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 12-15)
          - Correspondence regarding bequest and legacies, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 16)
        - Cutter, Charles Long: condolences, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 17)
        - Lindbergh, Charles Augustus, III (1930-32): death
          - Condolences to ECM, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
          - from Cleveland, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 20)
          - from Englewood, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 21)
          - from Abroad, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 22)
        - Morgan, Constance (Morrow): Milton Academy and threatening letters, 1929-39 (Box 24, Folder 23)
        - Morgan, Elisabeth Reeve (Morrow): death (Box 25)
          - Personal and family condolences, 1934-35 (Box 25, Folder 1)
          - Condolences, A-Z, 1934-35 (Box 25, Folder 2-6)
          - Typed copies of condolences, 1934-35 (Box 25, Folder 7)
          - Telegrams, 1934-35 (Box 25, Folder 8)
          - Funeral arrangements, obituary, and poetry, 1934-35 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - Dwight W. Morrow, Sr, 1931-54
          - Correspondence about DWM, 1931-54 (Box 26, Folder 2)
          - Biography by Harold Nicolson
            - Dwight Morrow: A Biography by Harold Nicolson, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 3)
            - ECM's notebook on biography (Box 26, Folder 4)
            - Correspondence
              - Selection of author and publisher, A-Z, 1932-35, undated (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
              - Lowry, Colonel Edward to ECM, 1933-34 (Box 26, Folder 8)
              - Nicolson, Harold to ECM, 1934-53 (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
              - Nicolson, Ben and Vita to ECM, 1934-39 (Box 26, Folder 11)
              - To ECM about biography after publication, 1935-44 (Box 26, Folder 12)
            - Photograph, financial arrangements with Nicolson, proof pages, 1901-35 (Box 26, Folder 13)
          - S.S. Dwight Morrow, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 14)
          - Death (Box 27)
            - Correspondence to ECM, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 1)
            - Condolences to ERMM
              - General, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
              - From abroad, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 4)
              - From Smith College and Milton Academy, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 5)
              - From Englewood, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
            - Tributes, clippings, articles, correspondence offering ECM Senatorship, 1931-32 (Box 27, Folder 8)
            - Memorial ceremony, correspondence, photographs, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - Dwight W. Morrow, Jr.
          - General, 1922-54 (Box 27, Folder 10)
          - Divorce and financial settlement, 1947-48 (Box 27, Folder 11)
          - Health: Dr. William Terhune, 1938-46 (Box 27, Folder 12)
          - Lincoln University and Fifth Avenue apartment, 1952-54 (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - Margot (Loines) Morrow, 1938-39 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Travel
        - China and Japan
          [see also: Organizations: Smith College: Ginling College]
          - United Board for Christian Colleges in China
            - Minutes, 1940-41 (Box 27, Folder 15)
            - Correspondence, 1937-48 (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
            - Printed material, 1947-48 (Box 27, Folder 18)
          - Printed material
            - Willis Lamott and Robert Speer, 1937-40 (Box 27, Folder 19)
            - Birth of a New China, Lin Yutang, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 20)
            - "What Would You Give to Make this a Short War?" and "A Letter from Madam Chiang Kai-shek," undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
            - "What Li Wen Saw," and University of Nanking brochures, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 22)
          - United China Relief: correspondence, conference, 1941-43 (Box 28, Folder 1)
          - Yenching University
            - Printed materials, 1929-47 (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
            - Correspondence, pamphlet, photograph, 1934-42 (Box 28, Folder 4)
              [see also: oversize]
          - Kobe College: correspondence, printed material, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 5)
          - Doshisha University, Japan: postcards, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
          - China: Peking photographs, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
          - Japan group photograph, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 8)
          - Women's Missionary Society, Presbyterian Church: report, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 9)
          - Notes and speeches, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 10)
            [see also: journal, spring 1936]
          - Notebook: trip to Orient, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 11)
          - Notebook, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
          - Peking Association of University Women annual meeting, Apr 1936 (Box 28, Folder 13)
          - Ginling College luncheon, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 14)
          - Smith College Club of Peking dinner, 25 Apr 1936 (Box 28, Folder 15)
          - Trip to Orient: correspondence, 1936-37 (Box 28, Folder 16)
          - Cook's handbook for overseas, 1935-36 (Box 28, Folder 17)
          - Twenty-five best views of Kandy and Up country, undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
          - R.M.S. Queen Mary menus, Sep-Oct 1936 (Box 28, Folder 19)
          - Visit to the Chinese Coast, Rev. Charles Gutzlaff, circa 1846-48 (Box 28, Folder 20)
          - Cook's India, 1935-36 (Box 29, Folder 1)
          - Orient itinerary, postcards, notes, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - Mexico
          - Art and archaeology
            - Watercolors by Amey Aldrich
              - "Trees of Mexico," undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
              - "Flowers of Mexico," undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
            - Sketches by Rene d'Harnoncourt, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 5)
            - Exhibition catalogs and bulletins, 1932-42 (Box 29, Folder 6)
            - Catalog of Frederick Davis painting exhibition, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 7)
            - Exposition of Indian tribal arts, 1931-32 (Box 29, Folder 8)
            - ECM's art objects on loan, 1941-44 (Box 29, Folder 9)
            - Diego Rivera murals and Stanton Catlin, 1929-50 (Box 29, Folder 10-12)
            - Photographs: Marion Freeman Wakeman and studio, 1937, undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
            - Photograph, correspondence: Diego Rivera fresco, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 14)
            - Report on archaeological exploration in Oaxaca, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence, 1929-48 (Box 29, Folder 16-27)
          - Financial (Box 30)
            - Account book, 1927-29 (Box 30, Folder 1)
            - Receipts and checkbook, 1928-54 (Box 30, Folder 2)
          - Household
            - Addresses, 1944-51 (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
            - Guest lists, 1944-51 (Box 30, Folder 5)
            - Dinner, 13 Sep 1927 (Box 30, Folder 6)
            - Cuernavaca house
              - Purchase, 1928-29 (Box 30, Folder 7)
                [see also oversize]
              - Rentals, 1931-36 (Box 30, Folder 8-10)
              - Maintenance, 1934-37 (Box 30, Folder 11-12)
              - Drawings, magazine articles (Box 30, Folder 13)
              - Correspondence, 1937-38, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
              - Household inventories, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 15)
            - Embassy inventory, 1927, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
            - Bateas (wooden bowls) inventory (Box 30, Folder 17)
            - Purchase of Mexican screen, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 18)
            - Book lists, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 19)
          - Notebooks
            - circa 1927-29 (Box 30, Folder 20-21)
            - circa 1931 (Box 30, Folder 22)
            - 1935-45 (Box 31, Folder 1)
            - 1952 (Box 31, Folder 2)
            - undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
            - Notes for speeches, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
          - Organizations
            - Estatutos de la Asociación Amigos de Taxco, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 5)
            - Mexico YWCA, 1929-33 (Box 31, Folder 6)
          - Printed materials
            - General, 1934, undated (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
            - Map of Mexico, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
            - Itineraries of a Motor Trip, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
            - American property/oil rights in Mexico, 1926 (Box 31, Folder 11)
            - El Indio, Jul 1929 (Box 31, Folder 12)
            - Bulletin of the Pan American Union, "A Glimpse of Mexico's Rural Schools," Oct 1930 (Box 31, Folder 13)
            - Mexican Art and Life, Jul 1938 (Box 31, Folder 14)
            - America's Future, "Mexico, Our Good Red Neighbor," Nov 1938 (Box 31, Folder 15)
            - Herring, "Cultural Relations with Latin America" and "The Unconquerable Mexican," by Samuel Inman, 1937-40 (Box 31, Folder 16)
            - "Passport to Mexico," Saturday Review of Literature, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 17)
            - "A Mexican Interpretation of Mexico," The Survey, by Rene d'Harnoncourt, 1 Oct 1930 (Box 31, Folder 18)
            - News clippings, 1927-49 (Box 31, Folder 19)
          - Travel arrangements
            - 1930 (Box 31, Folder 20)
            - 1940 (Box 31, Folder 21)
            - 1941 (Box 31, Folder 22)
            - 1944 (Box 31, Folder 23)
            - 1949-52 (Box 31, Folder 24-27)
            - 1954 (Box 31, Folder 28)
            - Trip itineraries, 1943-52 (Box 31, Folder 29)
            - Guide to Mexico city, 1939-54 (Box 32, Folder 1)
          - "Dwight Morrow and the New Understanding," undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
          - Macnab, Colonel AJ: speech on Mexico and DWM, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 3)
          - Book reviews by ECM, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
          - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - Other trips
          - Texas, Colorado, and Salt Lake City with Dillinghams: journal, Jun-Jul 1888 (Box 32, Folder 6)
          - Washington with Arthur Cutter: journal, 1889 (Box 32, Folder 7)
          - Europe: mementos, 1900-11 (Box 32, Folder 8)
          - France, 1918-19 (Box 32, Folder 9)
            [see also: Organizations: Smith College: Alumnae Association: War Service Committee]
          - Glacier Park: diary, 1919 (Box 32, Folder 10)
          - Nassau, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
          - Italy and Sicily
            - Notebook, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 13)
            - Artwork: Italian street vendors, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
          - England and Wales, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 15)
          - England: invitations to Coronation, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 16)
          - Europe: Welsh Choir, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence to family
      - Conover, Charlotte Reeve, 1922-43 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Cutter family, 1883-1905 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Cutter family, 1906-1945, undated (Box 33, Folder 1-6)
      - Cutter, Annie Spencer (1845-1938) and Charles Long, 1886-1912 (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
      - Cutter, Annie Spencer (1845-1938)
        - 1883-Jun 1895 (Box 33, Folder 9-13)
        - Sep 1895-May 1909, undated (Box 34, Folder 1-15)
        - May 1909-Dec 1917 (Box 35, Folder 1-15)
        - Jan 1918-Jul 1929 (Box 36, Folder 1-15)
        - Aug 1929-1938, undated (Box 37, Folder 1-12)
      - Cutter, Annie Spencer (1877-1957)
        - 1883-96 (Box 37, Folder 13-14)
        - 1897-1923 (Box 38, Folder 1-14)
        - 1924-54, undated (Box 39, Folder 1-12)
      - Cutter, Arthur, 1892-94 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Cutter, Charles
        - 1883-94 (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - 1895-1914 (Box 40, Folder 1-7)
      - Cutter, Rose, 1904 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Dillingham, Pauline, 1887-1951, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Hunt, Arthur, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Kelley, Rose Spencer, 1899-1904 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Lindbergh, Evangeline, 1929-34 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Lindbergh, Jon, 1941-43 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Morgan, Aubrey, 1935-52 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Morgan, Elisabeth Reeve (Morrow)
        - 1915-Oct 1922 (Box 40, Folder 15-18)
        - Nov 1922-34 (Box 41, Folder 1-12)
      - Morrow, Alice, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Morrow, Clara and James E., 1903-14, undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Morrow, Dwight Whitney (husband)
        - 1893-6 Oct 1901 (Box 41, Folder 15-17)
        - 1901-1930 (Box 42, Folder 1-7)
      - Morrow, Dwight Whitney, Jr., 1915-38 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Morrow, Jay J., 1927 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Morrow children, 1924 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Scandrett family, 1914-39 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Spencer, Mary, 1895-96 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Yates, Edith Cutter, 1895-1952 (Box 42, Folder 13-17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1915-45 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence from family
      - Cutter family, 1898-1953, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous, 1893-1953 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence with friends and associates (Box 43)
      - ECM to Aldrich, Amey, 1895-1953 (Box 43, Folder 1-4)
      - Aldrich, Amey to ECM, 1895-1953 (Box 43, Folder 5-11)
      - Aldrich, Amey: incoming and to Cutters, 1925-54, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - A - American Association of University Women (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - American Committee on Rights of Religious Minorities - Applegarth (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Archibald - Atwood (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Aubin - Bailey (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Barber - Bennett (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Bennington College - Bobbs Merrill Company (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Bloom - Bowdoin College (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Boyd - Browne (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Broz - Bunker (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Bunker - Burnett (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Burnett - Byrne (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - C - Chapin School (Box 44, Folder 9)